<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="recipe_name">
        <item>Spaghetti Bolognese</item>
        <item>Chicken Stir-Fry</item>
        <item>Caprese Salad</item>
        <item>Vegetarian Quinoa Bowl</item>
    </array>
    <array name="recipe_instruction">
        <item>
            In a large skillet, brown the ground beef over medium heat. Drain excess fat.
            \n Add chopped onions and minced garlic, sauté until softened.
            \n Stir in crushed tomatoes, tomato paste, oregano, basil, salt, and pepper. Simmer for
            20-30 minutes.
            \n Meanwhile, cook spaghetti noodles according to package instructions.
            \n Serve the Bolognese sauce over cooked spaghetti and garnish with grated Parmesan
            cheese.
        </item>
        <item>
            In a wok or large skillet, heat sesame oil over medium-high heat.
            \n Add sliced chicken and cook until browned and cooked through.
            \n Add garlic and ginger, stir-fry for 1-2 minutes.
            \n Add broccoli, bell pepper, and carrot. Cook until vegetables are tender-crisp.
            \n In a small bowl, mix soy sauce and hoisin sauce. Pour over the chicken and
            vegetables, toss to coat.
            \n Serve the stir-fry over cooked rice.
        </item>
        <item>
            Arrange tomato and mozzarella slices on a serving platter.
            \n Tuck fresh basil leaves between the tomato and mozzarella slices.
            \n Drizzle extra virgin olive oil and balsamic glaze over the salad.
            \n Sprinkle with salt and pepper to taste.
            \n Serve immediately as a refreshing salad or appetizer.
        </item>
        <item>
            In a saucepan, combine quinoa and vegetable broth. Bring to a boil, then reduce heat,
            cover, and simmer until quinoa is cooked and liquid is absorbed.
            \n In a bowl, assemble quinoa, black beans, corn, avocado, and cherry tomatoes.
            \n Drizzle with lime juice and sprinkle with chopped cilantro.
            \n Season with salt and pepper to taste.
            \n Toss the ingredients together before serving. Enjoy your nutritious quinoa bowl!
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="recipe_ingredient">
        <item>
            1 lb ground beef
            \n 1 onion, finely chopped
            \n 2 cloves garlic, minced
            \n 1 can (28 oz) crushed tomatoes
        </item>
        <item>
            1 lb boneless, skinless chicken breasts, sliced
            \n 2 cups broccoli florets
            \n 1 bell pepper, thinly sliced
            \n 1 carrot, julienned
            \n 3 tablespoons soy sauce
        </item>
        <item>
            4 large tomatoes, sliced
            \n 1 lb fresh mozzarella cheese, sliced
            \n Fresh basil leaves
            \n Extra virgin olive oil
            \n Balsamic glaze
        </item>
        <item>
            1 cup quinoa, rinsed
            \n 2 cups vegetable broth
            \n 1 can (15 oz) black beans, drained and rinsed
            \n 1 cup corn kernels (fresh or frozen)
            \n 1 avocado, sliced
            \n 1 cup cherry tomatoes, halved
        </item>
    </array>
    <array name="recipe_star">
        <item>2</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </array>
    <array name="time_cooking">
        <item>10</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </array>
</resources>